Stephen Landis

Front-End Web Developer

stephen.n.landis@gmail.com | stephenlandis.com | github.com/snlandis | linkedin.com/in/stephenlandis

About Me

As a front-end developer I help bring beauty and accessibility to website users while coordinating between back-end developers and designers. My experience in customer service and world travel has equipped me to be a team player anywhere I am while giving my best work for the user.

Tools and Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Wordpress, Git, React, Angular, jQuery, Node.JS, RESTful API, Express

Projects

- **Trivia Fight:** An app that allows players to log in, talk in a chat window, challenge each other via SMS invitation and answer trivia questions to win.
- **Philanthropeas:** A cross discipline effort between a UX team and my dev team. The idea behind the app was allow users to find a charity to donate extra food to or to register as a charity and coordinate donations.

Work Experience

Capstone Real Estate Services

January 2016 - September 2016

Staff Support Specialist

In 9 months I processed a year's worth of backlogged paperwork while keeping up with the day to day work load.

Noonday Collection

September 2015 - December 2015

Warehouse Generalist

Ensured customer orders were packed safely with the correct merchandise and were sent to the correct address.

Day & Night Waters

March 2013 - September 2015

Delivery Driver

Bottled water, loaded delivery trucks and delivered water to customers.

FedEx Express

October 2007 - January 2011

Courier

Handled coordination and delivery of time-sensitive letters and packages to clients.

Education

Web Development Immersive, General Assembly, Austin, TX

Completed 12-week immersive program that focused on front and backend technologies as well as databases and JavaScript frameworks.

Baylor University, Waco, TX